In this clip, we're going to talk about who invented homework.
I did some research on this.
And I have no idea, who invented homework.
Most people probably want to choke the guy who invented homework.
If you're a student.
But it's probably more important to talk about why homework was invented.
O.k.
It was not invented to make your life miserable.
Although, many students will probably think that.
But it was made so you could master a subject through a skill.
If you want to be an architect, you better be able to do your professor. Your architecture professor's homework. If not, you're going to be an architect.
If you're studying to be a doctor or a lawyer.
all your teachers are going to give you homework.
Now when you're in college, you don't have to do the homework.
It's not required.
But then, of course, when test time comes around.
If you didn't do your homework.
More likely, you're going to fail that test.
And you're not going to become an architect or lawyer or doctor.
Or whatever chosen field, you decided to pursue.
So who invented homework?
Maybe you can find that and let me know.
Because I don't know.